Downloaded @ subs4free.club
Fears of another wave intensify
as the worldwide death toll rises.
As Los Angeles enters its 213th
week of lockdown, the Health Department...
...the Health
Department has raised...
Experts are
reporting COVID-23 has mutated.
Today, Los
Angeles opened its first quarantine zone.
The Q-zone was created to
house the sick and the dying...
Anyone
with a fever will be taken to the Q...
The mortality rate
has risen to 56%.
Only the few people immune to
the virus are able to leave their homes.
Today, the CDC unveiled
designs for America's new immunity passes.
These passes come in
the form of canary yellow...
What?
Yeah, I got a delivery here.
You're late, asshole.
Just put it in the box.
UV sanitation activated.
UV sanitation complete.
- All good?
- No tip.
And tell Lester I want
a new delivery guy next time.
You just hate me
'cause I'm immune and you're not.
What did you say?
I said, "Don't forget
to toast the apocalypse."
Curfew is now in effect.
All unauthorized citizens
must stay indoors.
Remember the good old days of fake news?
Real news is worse.
Because any day,
the antibody test is coming.
Antibody test? I signed up for
that shit three years ago.
In a Burger King drive-through.
Guess what?
Burger King's gone.
What'd they tell us for the
last three years?
Stay home and wash your hands.
New data confirms
the virus attacks the brain tissue.
I've been hearing
a lot of weird rumors
about the institutional corruption
at the Department of Sanitation.
...will be
arriving in four to six hours.
You must not attempt
to leave your home.
Check out
the new immunity bracelet.
Literally, can't leave
the house without this.
I wonder if that's how
dinosaurs went. Just like...
The global death count
is now over 110 million.
It's the end of the world, bro.
As Los Angeles enters its 213th...
It feels like the apocalypse.
So, we just got to sit home,
like gerbils,
in our little bullshit cages.
Noncompliance
will be met with severe penalty.
- Guess what.
- Lockdown is in full effect.
There ain't no good news coming.
...or you will be
shot on sight.
Hey, Lester.
I'm held up, man.
They're checking bags,
they're checking tags.
Sanitation is on one today.
Stop messing around,
guys. Rich people need their shit!
Lester,
nobody's here for the pick-up.
I've been waiting
about 15 minutes.
Okay, turn that around
as soon as you can.
Jonie, you're 10 minutes late
getting to me. Come here.
Hey, man,
don't get bitchy with me.
Anthony, it's a left
on Fountain. Left!
Man, I'm turning left.
Put your left hand out,
check mark with the right.
Jeez, I gotta teach you your ABC's, too?
Oh, I'm going right. Sorry.
We're having a little delay.
We're seeing a new checkpoint
right there on Hollywood and Highland.
Kyle Kuzma, he advances.
He gets it to LeBron.
LeBron dunks for the win!
Yes, the crowd goes wild!
You made that priority drop yet?
It's next on my list.
"Priority" means
it's first on your list.
Lester, it's all the way
across town.
Hold up.
Are you at the court?
Uh... No.
I have GPS.
Then maybe.
Make a three for Kobe
and get going.
Hi, guys.
What's up? This is Larray.
My best friend
didn't pass his thermal scan
and the Department of
Sanitation took him to the Q-zone.
So, I'm worried, 'cause once you go
to the Q-zone, you don't ever leave.
Good morning, Marie.
Good morning, señora.
I cut some fruit for you
in the kitchen.
Thank you.
Good morning.
God, kid.
I have a question for you.
Yes?
So, I was wondering
about the whole Ellie thing.
Yeah, what about it?
So, her mom says that it's fine
if she comes and hangs out
for a little while.
I'm sorry. You know
we can't have people over.
All we're...
Not to mention, it is illegal.
What are you gonna do?
Call Sanitation
on two 12-year-olds?
Have them take us to the zone?
You keep pushing it,
and you might just find out.
Did you take your vitamins?
Yes, Mom.
Do you have your inhaler?
Uh-huh.
Okay, you're up.
Virus check in progress.
Three, two, one.
No virus defected.
Straight A's.
Have a great day.
So please go tell your dad
it's time to take the temp test.
Dad! Mom said it's time
for your temp test!
I could have done that.
...by order of the mayor,
who stated martial law
shall remain in place
for the foreseeable future.
Today, the Department of
Sanitation announced the opening
of a new Q-zone
in Boyle Heights.
The facility would be the fifth
of its kind established in the city
despite recent controversy
over a leaked report
describing conditions
in these zones as barbaric.
Virus check must be completed.
You have five minutes to...
Virus check in progress.
Three, two, one.
No virus defected.
Have a great day.
It's Nico,
from Lester's Gets.
Missus, the delivery boy
is here.
Great, these are ready to go.
Thank you.
Mmm-hmm.
UV sanitation activated.
Ready?
Do you
think we're just fish in a bowl to him?
UV sanitation activated.
UV sanitation complete.
Okay.
Thank you.
Really, thank you.
Go this way.
Yo, yo, yo!
Checking in per usual.
New strain, new year.
Isn't that great?
Looks like this one'll
kill you quick.
They're saying people who are catching
this are dropping dead within 48 hours.
Yesterday I saw
a 10-year-old girl
getting dragged from her
house and taken to the Q-zone.
Well, we know
what the "Q" stands for.
"Quick death."
All I'm saying is,
if you see those guys
in those big-ass yellow suits
coming up your block,
you better hide
your little sister.
Good evening, Miss Garcia.
Still on for date night?
Oh, every night.
You can't get rid of me.
You're such a stalker.
Yeah, well, it's easy when
my victim can't leave her home.
You're not missing
much out here.
Yeah, except for that view.
Oh, you like that?
This is my view, though.
I think mine's better. Say hi, Lita.
Hola, Nico. Cómo estás?
Hey, Lita. How are you?
Muy bien, Lita, y tú?
Estoy bien, y tú?
Nico, please don't fall.
I'm not gonna fall.
If I did, I wonder how long it would
take someone to find me out here.
Are you kidding?
Lester would have a cleanup
crew there in, like, 10 minutes, tops.
"Because a
dead courier is bad for business."
I sounded
just like him, didn't 1?
I'll see you later, stupid.
I miss you.
Give me an hour.
I got one more drop-off
I'm late for.
I'm not going anywhere.
Dozer, I need eyes
on one of my couriers.
High and tight.
Hello.
Yeah, Piper, um, it's Steve,
Gwen's husband.
You did that save the rhino
thing for us a few years back.
Oh, yeah.
That was a great party.
What can I do for you?
We, um...
We wanna take a trip
beyond the city limits.
Heard you might have the hookup.
Something to help us
get past the checkpoints.
Party will cost you 300 grand.
Done.
Okay, great.
Well, we'll be in touch.
Three apartment
buildings in Van Nuys were condemned today
after a number of residents
failed their daily virus check.
A spokesperson for the
Department of Sanitation
issued a response
to the outbreak
warning that the department was currently
completely overwhelmed by the caseload
and reminding citizens
that COVID is airborne.
No one should leave their home
for any reason.
...closed down in Echo Park.
I have eyes on the target.
Repeat, I have eyes
on the target.
What...
Stop! Show us your hands.
Hey, whoa, whoa! I'm immune!
Get on the ground! Now!
I'm immune!
He's got a bracelet.
Guy's immune.
Have him walk on.
Wow. You gotta be kidding me.
You guys really need to work
on your people skills.
No loitering. Oh, I'm sorry.
Am I holding up the line?
Keep it moving,
you munie scum.
Yeah, keep your mask on.
Don't take that mask off.
It's your boy Adam W.
Hey, check if out. So today,
I want to shout out all of our immune workers.
You mythical creatures,
you legends.
So, these munies live alone.
Total isolation.
Talk about social distancing.
And the whole time
they're out there,
they're getting coated in COVID.
It's in their hair,
their clothes.
And as one guy put it to me,
that shit sticks.
They can't go near
friends or family,
'cause they might get them sick.
Remember that the next time you're
pining for one of those yellow bracelets.
Good as new.
Whoo-hoo-hoo!
Thank you, Mrs. Griffin.
Spoke
to my buddy in Big Sur again.
He says they haven't had
a case in six months.
If only we could
get out of the city.
I'm still putting feelers
out to get black-market passes.
No hits yet,
but once we have those,
1 quarantine for three weeks
and then we're gone.
Hey, at least
you got your ride back.
More deliveries a day
means more money to save.
Who would have thought Lester's
Gets is actually good at getting things?
The man doesn't disappoint.
Tomorrow, Nico and Cielito
will ride again.
I still can't believe you named
that sick-ass bike Cielito.
I know, it's great, right?
No.
There she is.
Your one true love.
Here, check this out.
Hey, your garden's not dead.
Give it time.
God, I swear all I do is
love and nurture these things
and all they do is die on me.
We should take 'em
with us when we leave.
Lita has green fingers.
Oh, we're getting Lita
her own place, by the way.
Are we?
Uh, yeah.
I figure we have a lot of
lost time to make up for,
and we're not gonna want
a chaperone, are we?
I'm telling her you said that.
Do not tell her I said that.
I am.
You know I'm terrified of her.
That's why I'm telling her.
Bingo.
Hey, guys.
It's me, May. This is May Sings the Blues.
I'm a struggling
singer-songwriter
who still remembers
the good old days
when we could still
listen to music all together.
So, you can make any requests
and you can hit "like"
if you like what you hear
and maybe even subscribe.
So, what's next?
Let's lighten the mood
a little bit.
Vanilla Ice? No,
that's the wrong stream, buddy.
MDO0239 says,
"I remember you
played a great cover"
"of American Pie once."
"Your songs got me through some
rough days when I was in the military."
Well, MD,
this one is for you
and the boys.
Take a deep breath,
everything will be all right.
Leave your fears
On the battlefield.
Find your strength
and let it take the wheel.
Take a deep breath,
everything will be all right.
One step back,
Two steps forward.
And the beat of your heart
gets stronger.
One step back,
Two steps forward...
Ooh, ooh!
You still got it.
I see you.
Got a special
delivery for Miss Garcia.
Hey, stranger.
UV sanitation complete.
Package is successfully prepped.
"Roses are red,
violets are blue,"
"but I can't get those
in this screwed-up world,"
"so here's some pencils
for you."
You stole them,
Nicholas James.
How did I steal 'em?
There's nobody around.
They're just sitting there,
but if you don't want 'em...
No, no. Give me, give me,
give me, give me, please.
All right,
I'm putting 'em in.
UV sanitation complete.
Oh, my God.
I could kiss you right now.
Yeah, well, someday.
The way I figure, by the time
I'm 87 and you're, what is it, 84,
we should have
enough put away...
Shut up.
...to buy passes and get out of the city.
I'm serious.
It's a dream.
Oh, shit, Lester's calling me.
I'm gonna add him in.
What's up, boss?
What the hell are you doing?
Don't you have somewhere to be?
Like a high-priority drop
on the Westside?
I'm on it.
Say hi to Sara.
Hey, Lester.
Stop distracting
my best courier.
Whoa, whoa, whoa,
wait, wait, wait.
Did you just say,
"best courier"?
Slip of the tongue.
Now get going.
Well, you heard the man.
I gotta get going.
Yep.
I'll call you tonight?
I don't know.
I think I have to check my busy schedule,
but I think I can make it work.
User MD donated $100.
Well, buckle up.
Yeah, I'm gonna call you.
Hey, MD?
Uh, D... Dozer.
Like a bulldozer?
Uh, like Michael Dozer.
Hey, Michael.
I'm May.
It's nice to meet you.
No, I know you're...
You're May.
You miss if, Dozer,
the way things were?
I was on lockdown
long before it was fashionable.
How come?
When I got back from the war,
people didn't want
to talk about it.
You're a vet in a wheelchair,
people are...
They see you, they put their
face right in their phones.
They don't want to...
They don't want to have to face that.
Somewhere down the line,
I just
stopped going out.
For how long?
It's, uh...
It's coming up on six years.
Wow. You're a pro
at lockdowns.
This must be a cakewalk for you.
I don't know about a cakewalk,
for anybody, but
having Max... I mean,
Max here is my eyes and ears.
Hey, Max.
Is it as bad as it seems
out there?
It's worse.
It's way worse.
But it pays the bills.
$3,000.
It might as well have been 3 million.
What's the matter
with you tonight?
You look like
you lost your last friend.
How'd you like to go to...
I feel like I'm at the theater.
Yeah, you kinda
have to squint a little,
but, I mean, it's basically
like Mann's Chinese out here.
Hmm.
That was my favorite one.
You know I used to go there
every Friday for matinees, right?
Do you think that maybe we
were there for the same showings?
I did remember seeing this really
hot girl that I was too scared to talk to.
You're full of shit.
Where did you get the projector?
Another score
from the old office.
You really emptied
that place out, huh?
Oh, there's nothing left.
Everything's here.
I could make a law firm
out of my house right now.
I have paper, paper clips,
binders, highlighters, a hole punch.
I have a fax machine.
A fax machine?
Yeah, my mom would be proud.
She always said I'd
end up running the joint.
Can you see that?
There'll
be thousands of dollars there.
Actually, now that
you mention it,
would you mind telling the guy in
front if he could please remove his hat?
This guy right here?
Is that better?
Hey, Lita, you wanna
watch with us?
Go back to your
room and I'll bring you medicine, okay?
Is she sick?
Stay in your homes.
We are here to help.
Please remain in your homes.
Your safety is our priority.
If you attempt to leave your home,
you will be shot on sight.
Please remain in your homes.
What are you doing here?
Who's asking?
Lockdown is still in effect.
I am Emmett D. Harland,
Department of Sanitation.
Sara, what's going on?
I got out of Q-zone today.
I... I'm clean.
What are you doing?
Just bring it in.
Get away from me!
DOS is on-site. Standing down.
Heading to next callout. Over.
Department of Sanitation,
open up!
Shh.
Break it in, guys.
Hey, guys, guys!
It's the wrong apartment.
I said 3-2, 32.
Can you read?
Department of Sanitation.
They're coming for Alice.
Just break it down.
Mrs. Grant.
Alice and William Grant?
This is the Department of Sanitation.
By the power granted to me
by the City of Los Angeles,
I hereby detain you
under the ordinance 312
for immediate transport
to the Q-zone.
Sara, it's me!
Sara, do not open that door.
Do not open that door.
I'm coming over right now.
Please! Please help me!
Nico, please hurry.
Stop! No! Please!
Somebody help me, please!
Somebody help me!
Get off me!
Somebody, please!
I know you're in there.
Hello.
Are you Ms. Garcia?
I'm terribly sorry to inform you
that there's been an outbreak
of cases in this building,
including your poor neighbor.
Have you ever left
your apartment?
Maybe a glass of wine
with, uh, Mrs. Grant?
Like, a little gossip?
A little talk?
Breaking the lockdown?
No, we follow the rules here.
You wouldn't believe how many
times I've gotten that answer.
And before you know it,
I'm back at the same address.
That's...
Yeah, you know, it's...
Disobedience is, like,
spreading like a tornado.
Well, don't forget your
TempCheck in the morning.
And remember,
stay safe, sane and sanitized.
No! No, you have to
stay away from me.
Please,
just let me help you, okay?
For all we know,
it's just a cold, Lita.
No, Sara,
stay away from me.
Hey, I just got here.
How is she?
She's not good.
She has a fever.
Oh, shit.
Temp test
is at 9:00 a.m., Nico.
Okay.
They'll take us both.
You know that, right?
They'll take both her and me.
Sara...
Hey, hey.
No one's taking you from me.
She needs me. You should go,
okay? It's not safe here.
Yeah, right.
I'm not going anywhere.
Thank you.
Breaking curfew?
Oh, Jesus.
Harland needs to see me.
Oh, does he?
Yeah.
Mm.
He has those passes
that we need.
Mmm.
So may I leave?
You know, every time
you open that door,
you risk letting in
what's out there.
Yeah, I know. I also know
that it is the only way
that we are keeping
a roof over our heads.
Those are your words,
not mine. Jesus.
Piper, uh, you think
I want to go out there?
I think you love it.
And just because you wear that bracelet,
doesn't make it true.
So be a good boy
and burn that sleek
little outfit of yours
before you come
back into the house.
Nico?
I'm here.
She's sleeping.
She needs to rest.
It's like I can feel you
through this door.
Hey...
Do you remember
when we first met,
and you were yelling at me
in Spanish?
I have no recollection of that.
I blame Lester's handwriting.
It said 31,
but I read it as 37,
and I came pounding on
your door like a jackass.
Do you ever wonder
what would've happened
if you knocked
on some other girl's door?
Well, I knock
on a hundred doors a day.
But I've never met
anyone like you.
I'm really glad Lester
messed up that address.
Yeah, me too.
Oh, hey, Mom.
What are you still doing awake?
I heard voices.
Did Dad leave?
Yeah, he had to go out,
but he'll be back.
He shouldn't do that.
It's not safe.
I know.
But sometimes we have to do
things we don't want to survive.
Mom,
do you ever wish
I was different?
What? No, sweetie.
Wha... What do you mean?
Ellie said
with you being immune,
there's a 50% chance I would be.
Oh, honey.
And I'm not.
Instead, I'm even weaker
than a normal person.
You are not weak.
But if I wasn't like this,
you could go places.
You wouldn't have to
worry about me.
And why would
I wanna go anywhere
if you couldn't be with me?
Listen to me.
You are perfect.
Absolutely perfect.
And I wouldn't change
one thing about you.
And neither would your father.
Do you think she knows
she's a killer?
She's right next to him
And I'm sittin' by myself.
She's halfway in I think
She loves somebody else.
Shit.
But I love her.
Help, I'm feelin' overwhelmed.
Can't recognize myself.
Can you love somebody
If you love somebody else?
I need some help.
This aching hurts like hell.
There she is.
Hey, baby.
Do you like what you see?
Come here.
Is it worth the risk
coming to see me?
I guess we'll find out.
What do you want?
You know what I really want?
I don't want this.
And I don't want this.
Get this out of the way.
I want you.
Mmm-hmm.
It's time
for our temp test, okay?
Okay.
I'll go first, okay?
Mmm.
Virus check in progress.
Four, three, two, one.
No virus defected.
Have a great day.
Virus check in progress.
Four, three, two, one.
Virus check has failed.
A fever has been detected
at your residence.
Armed guards will be
arriving shortly.
You must not attempt to leave your
home or you will be apprehended.
Do not attempt to engage
with armed guards.
Bribes will not be accepted.
Your well-being is
our biggest priority.
It's gonna be okay.
Your compliance is mandatory
and appreciated.
Sara?
They're coming.
No, no, they can't.
You're not sick.
You know how this works, Nico.
If she's sick, I'm sick.
To hell with the rules, Sara.
Let's just go now.
Nico, I'm not leaving Lita.
It's gonna be okay.
You're going to be okay.
Sara, I'm not letting
you give up.
We were never
gonna get out of here.
I have to let you go, Nico.
Please say goodbye to me.
I'm not saying that, Sara.
I'm not saying that!
Please say goodbye to me.
I'm gonna get
the immunity passes, today.
How?
I'll figure it out.
I'm coming back, okay?
I'm coming back for you.
Okay.
Answer the phone.
Lester, I need
two immunity passes. Now.
What?
You think if I had a stash of
immunity cuffs hanging around,
I'd still be living
in this shithole?
Lester, please.
They're coming for Sara.
I have to get her out.
This is what happens when
you fall in love with a have-not.
I can't help you.
This building
is under full quarantine.
Look, all I need is a lead.
Just give me something.
You know them packages
you've been running
on the side for the Griffins...
Are you shitting me?
I've been running
black-market cuffs
and you didn't tell me?
Nico, listen,
you didn't hear this shit from me.
That asshole
is my biggest client,
but he's also a man...
Get lost.
...you do not
want to mess with.
Bracelets are 150 G's apiece.
You better have
the money to back it up.
I'll figure it out.
Lockdown is mandatory.
Noncompliance will be
met with severe...
Damn, kid.
Señor Nico.
How was Harland?
Nuts.
Hmm. Uh, passes for
Steve and Gwen are ready.
Are you sure we can trust them?
Everyone in my network
is reliable.
That's not who
I'm worried about.
What's... What's that
supposed to mean?
A courier is here.
Says he needs to speak
with you, Mr. Griffin.
Courier?
Thank you, Marie.
Yeah, Nico.
Mr. Griffin?
Yeah, what do you want?
I would never normally do this,
but it's an emergency.
I need two of these.
I heard maybe you can help me.
Mr. Griffin?
1... I don't know
what to tell you, kid.
I... I can't get those any
more than anybody else can.
Look, Mr. Griffin,
I have 13 grand.
I know that's nowhere
near enough, but it's all I...
How does he know about us?
I don't know.
Who've you been
shooting your mouth off to?
I haven't been shooting
my mouth off to anyone.
Why don't you ask your...
Your network, 'cause it's so "reliable"?
Do I need I remind you
what happens to us...
No... if people find
out what we're doing?
We go to jail, or even worse...
You do not. I know.
...we get thrown into
the Q-zone. Really?
And then what happens to Emma?
Piper, I told the kid
to go away.
What else do you want me to do?
I'd like to know
how he knows about us.
Well, why don't you do it?
Why don't you find out?
I'm so sick of
cleaning up your shit.
Uh, Nico?
Mrs. Griffin?
I think my husband
is just being extra cautious,
but I think I can help you.
Thank you, Mrs. Griffin.
Hey, listen, um, who...
Who told you about us?
Nobody. Nobody told me.
I just... I had nowhere to go,
so I came here.
I figured you guys
had connections.
Um, listen, we don't have
what you're looking for,
but, um, I know
someone who does.
Marie.
Can I give you what I have?
It's... It's not much.
I don't need your money.
UV sanitation activated.
Mrs. Griffin, you have
no idea how much this means.
Thank you,
and you're saving a life.
It's not done yet.
I have a lead.
I'm on my way there now. How's Lita?
She's not good.
There's armed guards outside my door.
Do not attempt
to leave your home.
I'll call you when I have the passes.
Just be ready, okay?
Okay.
Sara.
Hello?
Maria.
It's like La Scala in Milan.
You see,
in this country,
most people think
that Puccini is a mushroom.
You want a smoke?
No, I don't smoke.
Do you know what
I love about smoking?
It's nice to know there's something
out there that still can kill you.
Now, a little bird came flying,
landed on my shoulder,
whispered in my ear
that you need two passes.
Yeah.
Follow me.
Don't worry, I'm a regular guy like you,
just trying to make a living.
You're a munie, right?
So I assume these passes,
they're not for you?
No, my girl's grandma got sick.
Let's start
with the girl. Age?
Twenty-six.
Her full name
and social, please?
I need a name,
because I have to
program these passes.
You... You with me?
Sara.
I need her full name.
I get it. You gotta be cautious
and you gotta be smart,
especially these days,
you know.
I didn't set up this meeting.
You did.
And I'm here wasting
my goddamn time.
If you don't trust me, leave.
No.
I'm good.
You good?
You know, we're kinda lucky
because we're two munies.
I gave you my word.
And I would like to back it up
the old-fashioned way.
What do you say?
Good.
Feels good, doesn't it?
It's like a childhood memory.
A bite out of Grandma's cookies.
So I need the name of the girl,
and I need the name of whoever
knows about this meeting.
Do you understand?
And I can stick as many holes
in you as I like.
Guards! Just go in!
Get on the ground!
Come on!
What's your name, soldier?
Nico.
Nico, Boomer.
Why are you even helping me?
They drag and pull schmucks
like you down here to their death.
Today, I'm drawing
aline in the sand.
I like you, bro.
One dead body down here
stinks up the whole building.
Once you get that smell
in your nostrils, it lingers.
You can't blow it out.
Tired of it, man.
No more.
Over here!
Shit!
What are you doing?
I'm staying.
Head downstairs.
That'll get you back to the elevators.
Stay safe, pilgrim.
I'm rooting for ya.
Come on!
Oh, jeez.
How hard can it be, guys?
Hey!
Answer the phone.
Answer the...
Lester's Gets.
Distribution...
Cut the crap. Where is he?
Who are we talking about now?
Your courier, Nico.
He showed up here at my house
and he accused me of
selling black-market passes.
Well, he's not working today.
Don't bullshit me, Lester.
I... I know you sit there
and watch your guys drive
around all day like rats in a maze.
Just give me his GPS or I'm
gonna take my business elsewhere.
He, uh... looks like
he disabled his GPS.
I'll let you know
if he comes back online.
Yeah, you do that.
So?
He slipped the leash.
What do we pay Harland for?
He better get this contained.
Yeah.
So, it was pre-pandemic,
and I met this record exec online,
and he saw one of my
YouTube videos,
and he invited me out here,
and he told me that
I was gonna be a big star,
and then all the shit hit,
and I got trapped here.
And the record deal that
never existed now was gone.
It was never gonna happen.
He keeps doing
this weird dance with me
like somehow things
are gonna be different,
or somehow things are gonna be
the way that they were, but the...
You know that nothing...
Nothing is ever gonna be the same.
And I'm lonely, you know?
Well, this is nice
and light conversation.
You know what I mean?
I don't know why
I'm telling you all this.
What's the matter?
Are you okay?
What's going on? Nothing.
Is it that guy?
The suit you were
telling me about?
You gonna save me, Dozer?
I... I don't know if you're kidding or not.
Do you need saving? Do you...
'Cause I'll come over there.
No, it's okay.
If you got it,
you got it.
No, um, I'm gonna handle it.
Are you sure?
I'm gonna handle it.
Hey.
Hi.
What is it?
She's gone.
Please tell me
you have the passes.
I don't.
I don't have the passes.
It's okay.
Now I know
where I can get some.
But when they come,
you have to hide.
Okay? You cannot
let them find you.
You do whatever you
have to do, but just don't...
I need you to buy me
a little time.
Okay.
I'm sorry.
I love you.
I love you too.
Curfew is now in effect.
Daytime essential workers
must now return home.
Curfew is now in effect.
All essential workers must now return home.
Hey, I need to...
I need to see you tonight.
No, we...
We're done, okay?
What, are you playing hard to get?
You're driving me crazy.
Just... Please just
let me come over.
We don't have to do anything.
I just, I need to talk.
There's nothing to talk about.
And whatever this, um,
arrangement is, it's over.
May, come on,
don't do this.
I have tapes.
I have tapes of you promising
black-market immunity passes.
You were recording me?
It was just a little
life insurance policy.
You're dumping me on the phone!
William, leave me alone!
Or it all goes viral.
Okay?
Bitch.
What the hell?
Going out again?
What are you doing?
I know about your girlfriend.
So what?
Oh, no, you think I...
I care that you're screwing someone?
No, no. This is,
uh, about Emma, our daughter.
What chance does she have
if she gets this thing?
I don't know, Piper. What... What chance
do any of us have if we get this thing?
I want you out.
Give me the gun.
Piper, I don't have time for this.
Give me...
You let her tape you?
You dumb prick.
Give me the gun,
let me clean up my mess.
You want me to clean it up?
Give me the gun.
I want you out.
What are you gonna do?
You... You gonna shoot me?
Get out!
Get out.
Hello.
This is Piper Griffin.
I believe you know my husband.
I think we might be able
to help one another.
William's on his way
over to you.
I suggest that you not
be there when he arrives.
Thank you.
No.
No, no, no, no, Nico!
Hello.
Hi, uh, this is Lester
from Lester's Gets.
Uh, we're one big happy family.
Yeah, I know who you are.
It... It's Piper. What...
What can I do for you?
Yes, your husband
called me earlier today
looking for one of my couriers.
Yes, have you found him?
Yeah, I think so.
The thing is,
I think he's
inside your house.
Stay in your homes.
Repeat, stay in your homes.
If you attempt to leave your
home, you will be shot on sight.
If you attempt
to leave your home,
you will be met
with lethal force.
Help us to protect you.
Please remain in your homes.
I need you to
get up and get in the bathroom.
What's happening?
Come on, honey.
Shh...
Put this on.
What's going on?
Do not attempt
to leave your home.
Department of Sanitation! Open up!
Now, where is that girl?
You think you can hide?
I'll find you.
Bingo! Found Grandma!
Bag and tag the hag!
Hey, where are you?
Where the hell
is that little duckling?
Stay in your homes.
Repeat, stay in your homes.
My kingdom for a beer.
Nothing.
Oh, shi...
Roses are red,
violets are blue,
you think you can hide,
but I'll find you.
Lockdown is still in effect.
The Department of Sanitation
will relocate the infected.
Hey!
Hey, give me a hand with this!
Are you okay, Bobby?
Then get her outta here.
We have one deceased,
one in the wind. Over.
How dare you come into my house.
I'm not here to hurt anyone.
You've already put
my daughter's life at risk
just by stepping foot in here.
I came to you for help,
and you tried to have me killed.
Look, I just needed information
because I can't allow anyone
to know what we're doing here.
Nobody knows,
and no one will.
Mrs. Griffin, look,
I understand
you're just trying
to protect your daughter.
I get that.
Because I'm trying to save the one
person left in my life that matters to me.
I can't leave here
without that pass.
Please.
Please help me.
Top shelf.
Come on, get it down.
Open it up.
You better not
make me regret this.
This building
has been condemned.
The safest place
is your own home.
Department of Sanitation.
For containment you can trust.
Stay with the truck.
What's her name?
I assume it's a girl.
Sara Mia Garcia.
Now what?
Now we wait.
Stay in your homes.
We are here to help.
If you believe your neighbor
is defying mandatory lockdown,
give us a call.
Do you know
where you're gonna go?
Far away from here.
We're all just trying to
protect the ones we love.
Thank you.
Take care.
Oh, shit.
Hey, guys! Hold off!
Stop!
Okay, call them to stop.
Call them to stop!
The girl is in a Hazmat suit.
Secure all personnel,
girl is in disguise. Over.
Yeah. Yeah.
Hey, are you sure
it's okay if I come?
No, it's... It's fine.
Of course. Of course.
I'll see you soon.
Be safe getting over here.
Okay.
Oh, shit.
Goddamn it.
Come on. Come on.
Get out of the car, May.
You wanna play?
Please leave me alone! What?
You wanna play? Let's play!
Let's play! Get out!
Get out of the car
or I'll kill you.
Did you think you were
just gonna leave me?
I'll drag you out by your neck.
Get out! Get out!
Get out!
I'll pull you right through!
Tango is down.
We're at bingo fuel.
Recalling.
We're going.
We're going home.
Nice try.
Take this off.
Get it off.
Relax, breathe it in.
Breathe it in.
You don't get it, do you?
You're not stupid.
No symptoms
after being locked up
with your infectious grandma.
You'd be coughing up
your lungs right now,
and that makes you immune.
If that's true,
then let me go.
I'm so sorry.
That's not how it works.
Take her.
Sara!
Oh, no, no, no, no!
Well, she really
captured your likeness.
Talented girl.
Who are you?
Before this shit
started to hit the fan,
I used to drive garbage trucks
for the Department
of Sanitation.
Then all of a sudden
my superiors,
they started to die off.
And then one day,
I was running
the whole damn department.
I did it.
Four aces.
It's called the "Idiot." Look.
Happens once in a lifetime.
Emmett D. Harland,
once a lowly refuse collector,
is now the thin blue line
between death...
and a miserable existence.
Hey, uh, what about yourself?
What did you do before the fall?
I was a paralegal.
I was putting myself
through law school.
Oh.
Well, I guess it didn't
work out for everybody.
That's your problem, Nico.
You don't seem
to understand how good
us munies have it, huh?
Only a handful of us,
like you and me,
we're allowed to roam
around as we like.
You want a new car?
Just go to the dealership and drive it off.
Go into a house up in
the hills and just take over.
We're untouchable.
You see, munies,
we're not human anymore.
We're gods.
And how do you use
your godly power, huh?
You run around
and you try to save some
specimen that is bound to die.
I mean,
what's wrong with you?
You could have
the whole fucking world.
Where's Sara?
Oh, Sara? I don't know.
She's halfway to the
Q-zone by now, I guess.
I'm sorry.
You won't be joining her.
It's nice to know there's something
still out there that can kill you.
Answer the phone.
Answer the...
Nico?
I got something
1 gotta tell you.
Yeah, you told the Griffins
I was at their house.
Fair to say you owe me one?
I'm sorry, man.
There's a sanitation transport
headed for the Q-zone. I need to find it.
That ain't gonna be easy.
I have an ID, 0715-GLS.
I think I might know
someone who can help.
I've already mapped out
every route
from Sara's place to the zone.
We gotta search grid by grid.
Copy that.
Keep heading southeast.
We're not seeing anything behind you.
Ho... Hold up! Hold up!
Yup, 0715-GLS.
The truck is headed south on Western.
I repeat, south on Western.
We have visual confirmation.
Target is heading...
Heading east on 8th.
We got 'em.
Nico! We found her.
She's headed east on 8th,
just past Western.
They're almost at the zone,
so you better book.
I copy that.
You're not gonna
make it, man. Hurry up!
You have arrived
at Q-zone Alpha.
Welcome to Q-zone Alpha.
You must follow all directions.
All instructions are mandatory.
Prepare for immediate
processing.
Proceed to holding area
for decontamination.
Let's go.
Help me!
Just trust me, okay?
I trust you.
On your knees!
Get on your knees now!
Get on your knees!
Don't hurt her.
She's immune!
Scan the bracelet!
Scan it.
She's got a bracelet!
Run the ID.
She's good.
ID checks out.
I...
It's okay.
I'm like you.
Lester, it's Nico.
We got her.
We're getting out of here.
We're going home.
She's addicted to the IG.
Like it was an IV.
It's all about the money.
You'd think she wasn't ugly.
She can barely...
Lester. I hope
this finds you well, man.
Sara says hi.
It's been three months.
Feels like three years.
And the air out here,
you wouldn't believe it.
I can breathe again.
I wanted to thank you
for helping us get out.
And for helping a kid who
lost everything find a purpose.
You know, I realize now
we weren't just delivering packages.
We were delivering hope.
Harland and Griffin were reportedly
selling illegal immunity bracelets
to wealthy buyers
on the Westside.
And in a stunning revelation,
Griffin's own wife,
and a popular online streamer
who had evidence of the crimes,
worked together
to expose the conspiracy.
Always hiding all your problems.
You never try to solve them.
Mom?
Yeah?
Where's Marie?
She went home to her family.
She can barely.
Give it to me.
It's a good thing.
It's only ready.
That I'm the only.
These eyes
I see you.
I hope that one day
we can open our doors,
walk outside
and get back
to the things we love.
And you're
leaving me with the weight of the world.
These eyes
I see you.
And you're leaving me
with the weight of the world.
Whoo!
Man, I have missed the ocean.
This is incredible!
Whoo-hoo!
I don't know how many
packages we delivered together,
but now I'm sending you one.
But whatever you decide to do
with what's inside...
...promise me one thing.
Don't ever give up.
These eyes
I see you.
And you're leaving me.
The weight of the world.
Getting used to the dark.
But losing track of who we are.
You say I don't have to worry.
Oh, even though
We're miles apart.
Look at what we've become.
We're breathing hate
Through our lungs
I hope that
It's not contagious
'Cause I can taste it
On my tongue.
I can feel the tension.
Building like a question.
Chasin' a fire.
Oh, nobody can put it out.
We're put into cages
No one to save us now.
Yeah, I know you're tired.
Oh, but I know
You'll never break.
We turned our whole kingdom
Into a prison now.
And now we're breaking out.
Is it safe? Are we free?
Can't get rid of the memories.
Making me feel like
I'm drowning
'Cause it keeps playing
On repeat.
I don't know how it ends.
Our hearts are craving
For revenge.
Imagine that it's not forever.
Oh, and we get to start again.
Chasin' a fire.
Oh, nobody can put it out.
We turned all our kingdom
Into a prison now.
But now we're breaking out.
Subtitles by explosiveskull
Provided by SilverStark